Md Wasif Alamgir

Highly adaptable, plug-and-play attitude with 2.5+ years of experience in delivering solutions from defining the problem to the final consumption framework. Ahead of schedule and under budget. Seeking opportunity to leverage advanced data analysis, data management, and quality assurance skills.

wasifalamgir@gmail.com

+919903910034

Bangalore, India

air Ba

linkedin.com/in/ md-wasif-alamgir

github.com/AlamgirWasif/Analysis_Project

WORK EXPERIENCE

Project Service CoordinatorDiversified

02/2023 - Present

Bangalore, India

Tasks

- Prepare monthly and weekly reports and dashboards based on Power-BI.
- Working on Vendor charges and client billings from start to end of the service cycle.
- Invoice dispute management for both client as well as vendor bills.
- Liaise with IT, sales engineers, account receivables and payables, and account managers to ensure delivery of successful services.
- Manage Vendor & Client Relationships.
- Ensure that service deadlines and service level agreement are met.
- Coordinate Managed Services for major retail locations and financial institutions.

Senior Operations Analyst Amazon Development Centre

07/2022 - 01/2023

Bangalore, India

Tasks

- Worked extensively with DML SQL queries to pull raw data to analyze products and prices.
- Performed Exploratory Data Analysis on daily basis using EXCEL, using functions like VLOOKUP, Pivot table, etc.
- Responsible for creation of weekly and monthly reports on Excel as well as dashboards using Power-BI for both internal and external stakeholders.
- Responsible for analyzing trends and patterns in the data to find best prices and available products.

Operation Analyst

Amazon Development Centre

12/2020 - 06/2022

Bangalore, India

Tasks

- Analyzed a minimum of 30 Competitor websites on daily basis and demand-supply trends as per page views. Also, monitored deals, discount offers, Pre-launch products, flyers, offline prices for the top websites.
- Involves key decision making through detailed analysis of 7 product-line-up comprising of more than 50 different varieties of products based on multiple parameters.
- Worked on analyzing data to perform proper and accurate data mapping between data set and competitor data.
- Worked out through meeting the monthly productivity targets under high work pressure while also exceeding and maintaining the minimum required efficiency rate of 99.75%.

SKILLS

Power-BI MySQL MS Excel Data Analysis

Data Visualization Data Modelling Python

PROJECT

Sales Insights - Brick & Mortar business [Power-BI | MySQL]

- **–** ETL has been performed on the Atliq Hardware Stores Data.
- Data Modelling has been performed between the tables of the dataset.
- Designed a Power BI dashboard to understand AtliQ hardware goods sales trend.
- Created KPI cards displaying Month-Over-Month and Year-Over-Year change in sales and quantity.
- Dashboard has been created to show complete breakdown of revenue and profit based on Region, States and Products.
- Complete performance insight chart has been created to show customer insights based on past and current year data.
- The final dashboard was effective at displaying the sales trend of AtliQ hardware, allowing users to understand the data and make informed decisions.

INTERESTS

Current Affairs Anime

Following Latest Technology

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration

The Bhawanipur Education Society College, Calcutta University

ISC

Grace Ling Liang English School

ICSE

Grace Ling Liang English School